A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 1 FA1292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships and Grants, 1951-1996, 2002; 2
  - 57-400, Keio University, Building Annex, Bacteriology & Pathology, 1957-1958 (Box 59, Folder 804)
  - 58-441, Keio University, Journals-Back Numbers, 1958-1960 (Box 59, Folder 805)
  - 58-450, Keio University, Animal Laboratory, 1958-1959 (Box 59, Folder 806)
    2014:022, SG 1:043
  - 58-450, Keio University, Animal Laboratory, 1958-1959; 2014:022, SG 1:043
  - 60-523, Keio University, Building-Biochemistry & Pharmacology, 1960-1962 (Box 59, Folder 807)
  - 61-603, Keio University, Library Remodeling, Local Purchases, 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 808)
  - 62-629, Keio University, Building Construction & Equipment-Central Workshop, 1962-1964, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 809)
  - 63-705, Keio University, Biochemistry & Pharmacology Equipment, 1963-1965 (Box 60, Folder 810)
  - 63-719, Keio University, Audio-Visual Center, Remodeling-General Correspondence, 1960, 1963-1965 (Box 60, Folder 811)
    2014:022. SG1:044
  - 63-719, Keio University, Audio-Visual Center-Remodeling-General Correspondence, 1960, 1963-1965; 2014:022, SG 1:044
  - 64-779, Keio University, Equipment-Central Research Laboratory, 1964-1965 (Box 60, Folder 812)
  - 65-806, Keio University, Equipment-Germ Free Laboratory, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 813)
  - 65-850, Keio University, Supplies & Equipment, Machine Shop-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 814)
  - 57-397-25, Keio University, Fellow, Aizawa, Toyozo, 1958-1959 (Box 60, Folder 815)
  - 58-429-9, Keio University, Fellow, Akakura, Ichiro, 1958-1959 (Box 60, Folder 816)
  - 67-938-45, Keio University, Fellow, Akasaka, Keijiro, 1967-1969 (Box 60, Folder 817)
  - 60-541-17, Keio University, Fellow, Asami, Keizo, 1960, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 818)
  - CM 279-18, Keio University, Fellow, Asano, Seiichi, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 819)
  - 63-694-54, 65-834-1, 65-868-13, Keio University, Fellow, Fukudome, Takao, 1962-1966 (Box 60, Folder 820)
  - 63-694-55, 65-834-20, Keio University, Fellow, Homma, Mitsuo, 1964-1965 (Box 60, Folder 821)
  - 67-936-10, Keio University, Fellow, Hosoda, Yasuhiro, 1966-1967 (Box 60, Folder 822)
  - 62-647-7, Keio University, Fellow, Ikeda, Kameo, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 823)
  - 68-022-19, Keio University, Fellow, Kaneko, Akimichi, 1968, 1970, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 824)
  - 62-591-12, Keio University, Fellow, Kondo, Haruo, 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 825)
  - CM 279-16, Keio University, Fellow, Kudoh, Tatuyuki, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 826)
  - 58-429-29, Keio University, Fellow, Kusama, Yoshio, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 827)
  - 57-397-213, Keio University, Fellow, Matsubayashi, Hisakichi, 1957-1958, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 828)
  - 70-141-18, 71-203-19, Keio University, Fellow, Muraki, Takamura, 1970-1972, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 829)
  - 69-086-22, Keio University, Fellow, Ohta, Yasuyo, 1968-1970, 1972, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 830)
  - Cm 279-17, Keio University, Fellow, Ojima, Nobuo, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 831)
  - 68-022-61, 69-086-66, Keio University, Fellow, Sakuraki, Haruhiko, 1969-1970 (Box 60, Folder 832)
  - 59-474-6, Keio University, Fellow, Sambe, Ken, 1959-1960, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 833)
  - 65-834-54, Keio University, Fellow, Shigeta, Sadayoshi, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 834)
  - 65-834-9, Keio University, Fellow, Shiinea, Eiichi, 1963-1965 (Box 60, Folder 835)
  - 58-429-17, Keio University, Fellow, Shimada, Nobukatsu, 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 836)
  - 62-647-9, Keio University, Fellow, Yokoyama, Tetsuro, 1962-1964 (Box 60, Folder 837)
  - 65-868-2, Keio University, Fellow, Tsuda, Yoshinari, 1965-1966 (Box 60, Folder 838)
  - 59-492, Keio University, Visiting Professor, Greifenstein, Ferdinand Ernest, 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 839)
  - CM 249, Keio University, Visiting Professor, Johnston, Charles G., 1957-1958, 1960, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 840)
  - CM 259-7, Keio Gijuko University, School of Medicine, Fellow, Kusama, Yoshio, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 841)
  - Kobe Medical College, 1959, 1965, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 842)
  - Kobe University, General, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 843)
  - CM 365, Kobe University, Equipment-Physiology, 1956-1957 (Box 61, Folder 844)
  - 60-549, Kobe University, Construction & Equipment-Medical Library, 1959-1961 (Box 61, Folder 845)
    2014:022, SG 1:045, 2014:022, SG 1:046
  - 60-549, Kobe University, Construction & Equipment-Medical Library, 1959-1961; 2014:022, SG 1:045
  - 60-549, Kobe University, Construction & Equipment-Medical Library, 1959-1961; 2014:022, SG 1:046
    oversized architectural drawings
  - 62-658, Kobe University, Equipment-Physiology, 1962-1965 (Box 61, Folder 846)
    2014:022, SG 1:047
  - 62-658, Kobe University, Equipment-Physiology, 1962-1965; 2014:022, SG 1:047
  - 64-741, Kobe University, Library Support, 1964-1965, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 847)
  - 67-971, Kobe University, Computer Components, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 848)
  - 64-762-17, Kobe Medical College, Fellow, Hotta, Susumu, 1964-1966 (Box 61, Folder 849)
  - 59-474-7, Kobe Medical College, Fellow, Kashiwagi, Daiji, 1959-1960 (Box 61, Folder 850)
  - 60-541-19, Kobe Medical College, Fellow, Kuromaru, Shoshiro, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 851)
  - 67-938-50, Kobe University, Fellow, Sera, Kazuaki, 1965-1968, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 852)
  - 65-834-28, Kobe Medical College, Fellow, Shibuya, Yoshio, 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 853)
  - 61-591-41, Kobe Medical College, Fellow, Tomomatsu, Tatsuya, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 854)
  - 62-647-21, Kobe Medical College, Fellow, Yamori, Takeo, 1961-1963 (Box 61, Folder 855)
  - 64-762-16, Kobe Medical College, Fellow, Yorifuji, Susumu, 1964-1965 (Box 61, Folder 856)
  - Kurume University, General, 1958-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 61, Folder 857)
  - CM 292, Kurume University, School of Medicine, Books, Journals, & Equipment, 1953-1956 (Box 61, Folder 858)
  - CM 385, 58-442, Kurume University, Equipment-Pre-clinical Laboratories, 1956-1961 (Box 61, Folder 859)
  - 59-479, Kurume University, Equipment-Cardiology Laboratory & Clinical Pathology, 1959-1961 (Box 61, Folder 860)
  - 61-591-11, Kurume University, Fellow, Funatsu, Iichiro, 1955, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 861)
  - CM 362-12, Kurume University, Fellow, Okabe, Koyo, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 862)
  - 68-022-37, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Hasegawa, Eiichi, 1968-1970 (Box 61, Folder 863)
  - 62-647-39, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Kitagawa, Shiro, 1962-1964 (Box 61, Folder 864)
  - 65-834-34, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Kitasato, Miroshi, 1965, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 865)
  - 58-429-38, 60-541-7, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Konishi, Teruo, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 866)
  - 64-762-38, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Kusunoki, Tomoichi, 1962, 1964-1965 (Box 62, Folder 867)
  - 68-022-18, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Machino, Mitsuo, 1967-1968 (Box 62, Folder 868)
  - 62-647-38, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Nagata, Hisanori, 1962-1964 (Box 62, Folder 869)
  - CM 362-13, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Nakamura, Fumio, 1957 (Box 62, Folder 870)
  - 64-762-35, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Sano, Yutaka, 1963-1965 (Box 62, Folder 871)
  - 65-834-32, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Sasaki, Takahi, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 872)
  - 59-474-28, 60-541-50, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Shimade, Nobuo, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 873)
  - 61-591-15, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Yoshida, Yukio, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 874)
  - 60-541-3, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Yoshimura, Hisato, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 875)
  - 57-397-27, Kyoto Prefectural University of Medicine (KPUM), Fellow, Yuge, Tunekazu, 1958-1959
  - 61-604, Kyoto University, Research-Biochemistry, 1961-1963 (Box 62, Folder 876)
  - 62-652, Kyoto University, Reconstruction & Equipment-Biochemistry Department, General Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 62, Folder 877)
  - 63-707, Kyoto University, Equipment-Biochemistry, 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 878)
  - 63-720, Kyoto University, Library Building, General Correspondence & Original Request, 1963-196 (Box 62, Folder 879)
  - 64-770, Kyoto University, Equipment-Biochemistry, 1964-1965 (Box 62, Folder 880)
  - 66-878, Kyoto University, Library Support, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1965-1970 (Box 62, Folder 881)
  - 66-911, Kyoto University, Equipment-Biochemistry, 1966-1970 (Box 62, Folder 882)
  - 64-762-36, Kyoto University, Fellow, Fukami, Yasushi, 1964-1967 (Box 62, Folder 883)
  - CM 311-11, Kyoto University, School of Medicine, Fellow, Hirasawa, Ko, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 884)
  - 59-474, Kyoto University, Fellow, Horii, Isoo, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 885)
  - 65-834-31, Kyoto University, Fellow, Ito, Tetsuo, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 886)
  - 68-022-39, Kyoto University, Fellow, Kinoshita, Masahiko, 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 887)
  - 60-541-26Kyoto University, Fellow, Kotani, Mashiko, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 888)
  - CM 327-8, Kyoto University, School of Medicine, Fellow, Minoguchi, Gen, 1955-1956 (Box 62, Folder 889)
  - 66-896-21, Kyoto University, Fellow, Mizuno, Noboru, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 890)
  - 58-429-31, Kyoto University, Fellow, Nagai, Hideo, 1959 (Box 62, Folder 891)
  - 64-762-53, Kyoto University, Fellow, Nishio, Masashichi, 1964-1965 (Box 62, Folder 892)
  - 68-022-29, Kyoto University, Fellow, Nosaka, Shoichiro, 1968-1970 (Box 62, Folder 893)
  - CM 327-23, Kyoto University, Fellow, Ogiu, Kikuo, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 894)
  - 62-647-20, Kyoto University, Fellow, Okamoto, Michio, 1962-1963 (Box 62, Folder 895)
  - 60-541-34. Kyoto University, Fellow, Okuda, Rokuro, 1961, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 896)
  - 65-834-37, 66-896-46, Kyoto University, Fellow, Seiki, Kanji, 1965-1967 (Box 62, Folder 897)
  - 64-762-37, Kyoto University, Fellow, Takano, Kiichi, 1964-1966, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 898)
  - 62-647-37, 63-694-40, Kyoto University, Fellow, Takeshita, Hiroshi, 1962-1964 (Box 62, Folder 899)
  - 65-834-39, Kyoto University, Fellow, Tanaka, Seisuke, 1964-1965 (Box 62, Folder 900)
  - 67-938-39, Kyoto University, Fellow, Tanimura, Takashi, 1967-1968 (Box 62, Folder 901)
  - 62-647-16, Kyoto University, Fellow, Taniuchi, Hiroshi, 1962-1964 (Box 63, Folder 902)
  - 61-591-23, Kyoto University, Fellow, Yokoyama, Ikuzo, 1961-1963 (Box 63, Folder 903)
  - 62-659, Kyoto University, Visiting Professor, Feigelson, Philip, Biochemistry, 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 904)
  - 65-802, Kyoto University, Visiting Research Fellow, Olson, James A., 1964-1965 (Box 63, Folder 905)
  - CM 379, Kyushu University, Equipment-Library, 1956-1957 (Box 63, Folder 906)
  - 59-502, Kyushu University, Construction-Library, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 907)
  - 60-550, Kyushu University, Equipment, 1960-1962 (Box 63, Folder 908)
  - 61-605, Kyushu University, Equipment-Physiology, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 909)
  - 62-660, Kyushu University, Equipment-Bacteriology, 1962-1964 (Box 63, Folder 910)
  - 64-742, Kyushu University, Equipment-Biochemistry, 1964-1965 (Box 63, Folder 911)
  - 57-397-3, Kyushu University, Fellow, Amako, Tamikazu, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 912)
  - 58-429-30, Kyushu University, Fellow, Enjoji, Munenori, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 913)
  - 57-397-1, Kyushu University, Fellow, Fujino, Hiroshi, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 914)
  - 60-541-25, Kyushu University, Fellow, Hasegawa, Kazuo, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 915)
  - 59-474-5, Kyushu University, Fellow, Inokuchi, Kiyoshi, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 916)
  - 60-541-23, Kyushu University, Fellow, Inoue, Tokuji, 1960-1962 (Box 63, Folder 917)
  - 63-694-22, Kyushu University, Fellow, Ishii, Yoichi, 1963-1969 (Box 63, Folder 918)
  - 62-647-24, Kyushu University, Fellow, Ishinishi, Noburu, 1962-1963 (Box 63, Folder 919)
  - CM 327-27, Kyushu University, Fellow, Kanehisa, Takuya, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 920)
  - 59-474-38, Kyushu University, Fellow, Katsuki, Shibanosuke, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 921)
  - 66-896-60, Kyushu University, Fellow, Kawashima, Kenjiro, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 922)
  - 68-022-27, Kyushu University, Fellow, Kumazawa, Jyoichi, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 923)
  - 65-834-35, Kyushu University, Fellow, Kuroiwa, Yoshigoro, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 924)
  - CM 311-17, Kyushu University, School of Medicine, Fellow, Mitsuno, Takao, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 925)
  - 67-938-48, Kyushu University, Fellow, Tachibana, Nobuyoshi, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 927)
  - 62-647-13, Kyushu University, Fellow, Takemitsu, Yoshiharu, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 928)
  - 57-397-19, Kyushu University, Fellow, Toda, Tadao, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 929)
  - 62-647-46, Kyushu University, Fellow, Wansano, Takeo, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 930)
  - 62-762-11, Kyushu University, Fellow, Yumoto, Tokichi, 1964, 1967-1968 (Box 63, Folder 931)
  - 61-606, Nagasaki University, Library Furnishings & Equipment, General Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 63, Folder 932)
    2014:022, SG 1:048
  - 61-606, Nagasaki University, Library Furnishings & Equipment, General Correspondence, 1960-1962; 2014:022, SG 1:048
  - 61-721, Nagasaki University, Equipment, Teaching & Research-Biochemistry, 1963-1964 (Box 63, Folder 933)
  - 64-745, Nagasaki University, Equipment-Biochemistry, 1963-1966 (Box 63, Folder 934)
  - 64-746, Nagasaki University, Equipment-Pathology, 1964-1967 (Box 63, Folder 935)
  - 65-851, Nagasaki University, Equipment-Pharmacology-Physiology Student Laboratory, 1965-1967 (Box 63, Folder 936)
  - 68-037, Nagasaki University, Equipment, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1968-1969 (Box 63, Folder 937)
  - 67-938-34, Nagasaki University, Fellow, Hashiba, Kunitake, 1967, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 938)
  - 60-541-32, Nagasaki University, Fellow, Hayashi, Ichiro, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 939)
  - 65-834-41, 67-936-16, Nagasaki University, Fellow, Maeda, Renju, 1965, 1967, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 940)
  - 63-694-38, Nagasaki University, Fellow, Maeda, Syozo, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 941)
  - 66-896-52, 67-938-51, Nagasaki University, Fellow, Miura, Hajime, 1966-1968 (Box 64, Folder 942)
  - 65-834-42, Nagasaki University, Fellow, Okajima, Shunzo, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 943)
  - 68-022-36, Nagasaki University, Fellow, Seki, Tomomi, 1965-1966, 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 944)
  - 60-541-33, Nagasaki University, Fellow, Tsuji, Yasikuni, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 945)
  - CM 279-1, Nagoya Medical School, Fellow, Itoh, Shingi, 1953-1954, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 946)
  - CM 259-20, Nagoya University, Fellow, Okada, Hitoshi, 1953-1954 (Box 64, Folder 947)
  - CM 311-20, Nagoya University, Fellow, Takahashi, Shinji, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 948)
  - 58-429-32, Nagoya University, Fellow, Togari, Chikataro, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 949)
  - 59-474-23, Nagoya University, Fellow, Yamada, Kazumaro, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 950)
  - 61-591-13, Nagoya University, Fellow, Yamamoto, Sadahiro, 1961, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 951)
  - CM 327-6, Nihon University, College of Medicine, Fellow, Tanabe, Junichi, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 952)
  - 59-503, Niigata University, Equipment-Library Microfilm, 1959-1960, 1962-1963 (Box 64, Folder 953)
  - CM 327-24, Niigata University, Fellow, Matsuda, Katsuichi, 1956 (Box 64, Folder 954)
  - 60-541-31, Niigata University, Fellow, Mikuni, Masakichi, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 955)
  - 64-647-25, Niigata University, Fellow, Miyamura, Sadao, 1962-1964 (Box 64, Folder 956)
  - 65-834-43, Niigata University, Fellow, Niijima, Akira, 1965-1967 (Box 64, Folder 957)
  - 59-474-24, Niigata University, Fellow, Sakai, Tetsuro, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 958)
  - 57-397-24, Niigata University, Fellow, Yakata, Minoru, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 959)
  - 59-507, Okayama University, Equipment-Parasitology Department, Electron Microscope, 1959-1960 (Box 64, Folder 960)
  - 64-780, Okayama University, Library Construction, 1963-1964 (Box 64, Folder 961)
    2014:022, SG 1:049
  - 67-938-64, Okayama University, Fellow, Aoyama, Hideyasu, 1967-1968 (Box 64, Folder 962)
  - 59-474-27, Okayama University, Fellow, Hamamoto, Eiji, 1960 (Box 64, Folder 963)
  - 66-896-28, Okayama University, Fellow, Hirabayashi, Koji, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 964)
  - 61-591-21, Okayama University, Fellow, Hukuhara, Takesi, 1961-1962 (Box 64, Folder 965)
  - 57-397-26, Okayama University, Fellow, Inatomi, Seiiti, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 966)
  - 61-591-14, Okayama University, Fellow, Kitamura, Isamu, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 967)
  - 60-541-24, Okayama University, Fellow, Mochizuki, Yoshio, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 968)
  - 62-647-19, Okayama University, Fellow, Nagashima, Hideo, 1963-1964 (Box 64, Folder 969)
  - 63-694-15, 65-834-2, 66-896-25, Okayama University, Fellow, Ogata, Takuro, 1963, 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 970)
  - 58-429-33, Okayama University, Fellow, Omori, Toyoko, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 971)
  - CM 279-2, Okayama University, Medical School, Fellow, Yagi, Hideo, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 972)
  - 61-572, Okayama University, Visiting Lecturer, Liebelt, Robert A., 1961 (Box 64, Folder 973)
  - 58-451, Osaka University, Equipment & Furnishings-Library, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 974)
  - 59-505, Osaka University, Equipment-Library, 1959-1960 (Box 64, Folder 975)
  - 60-561, Osaka University, Journals & Equipment, 1960-1962 (Box 64, Folder 976)
  - 62-661, Osaka University, Library Support, 1962, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 977)
  - 63-680, Osaka University, Library Support, 1963-1966 (Box 64, Folder 978)
  - 65-841, Osaka University, Equipment-Pathology, 1965-1969 (Box 64, Folder 979)
  - 68-036, Osaka University, Equipment-Anatomy, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1972 (Box 64, Folder 980)
  - 63-694-57, Osaka University, Fellow, Hashimoto, Paulo Hitonari, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 981)
  - 63-694-24, Okasa University, Fellow, Ishida, Kenzo, 1963-1964 (Box 65, Folder 982)
  - 60-541-40, Osaka University, Fellow, Kaneko, Ziro, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 983)
  - 58-429-37, Okasa University, Fellow, Kawata, Hajime, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 984)
  - 63-694-13, Okasa University, Fellow, Kondo, Shichiro, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 985)
  - 60-541-22, Osaka University, Fellow, Kusunoki, Takamitsu, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 986)
  - 60-541-29, Osaka University, Fellow, Ozawa, Yasuro, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 987)
  - 62-647-18, 63-694-32, Osaka University, Fellow, Sonoda, Takao, 1962-1963 (Box 65, Folder 988)
  - 64-762-31, 65-868-15, Osaka University, Fellow, Takashima, Yoichiro, 1964-1966 (Box 65, Folder 989)
  - 59-474-21, 61-591-34, Osaka University, Fellow, Taki, Ichiro, 1959-1960, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 990)
  - 61-591-18, Osaka University, Fellow, Uedam Takashi, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 991)
  - 68-022-28, 69-086-43, Osaka University, Fellow, Uozumim, Tohru, 1968-1970 (Box 65, Folder 992)
  - 66-897, Osaka University, Visiting Professor, Pathology, Stoddard, Leland D., 1966 (Box 65, Folder 993)
  - 59-477, Sapporo Medical College, Library Support, 1959-1964 (Box 65, Folder 994)
    2014:022, SG 1:050
  - 59-477, Sapporo Medical College, Library Support, 1959-1964; 2014:022, SG 1:050
    Oversized poster with photographs-Gifted from the Chine Medical Board
  - 61-607, Sapporo Medical College, Library Support, 1959-1964 (Box 65, Folder 995)
    2014:022, SG 1:051 and 2014:022, SG 1:052
  - 61-607, Sapporo Medical College, Library Support, 1959-1964; 2014:022, SG 1:051
    Oversized architectural drawings-(2) Library building Annex (9) furniture designs
  - 61-607, Sapporo Medical College, Library Support, 1959-1964; 2014:022. SG 1:052
    Oversized architectural drawing-Plans for Adding Student Conference Room and Increase the Number of Reading Room Seats
  - 62-662, Sapporo Medical College, Equipment & Supplies, 1962-1965 (Box 65, Folder 996)
  - 63-708, Sapporo Medical College, Library Support, 1963-1965 (Box 65, Folder 997)
  - 63-722, Sapporo Medical College, Equipment-Experiment Surgery Laboratory, 1963-1965 (Box 65, Folder 998)
  - 65-842, Sapporo Medical College, Library Support, 1965-1968 (Box 65, Folder 999)
  - 65-852, Sapporo Medical College, Equipment-Teaching, 1965-1966, 1968-1970 (Box 65, Folder 1000)
  - 65-834-48, Sapporo Medical College, Fellow, Nakagawa, Takashi, 1965-1966 (Box 65, Folder 1001)
  - 67-938-32, Sapporo Medical College, Fellow, Takahashi, Kyozo, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 1002)
  - 68-022-48, Sapporo Medical College, Fellow, Tanaka, Nobuyuki, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 1003)
  - 66-933, Sapporo Medical College, Visiting Professor, Mark, Lester C., 1966-1968 (Box 65, Folder 1004)
  - 58-452, Tohoku University, Equipment-Library Microfilm, 1958-1959 (Box 65, Folder 1005)
  - 59-498, Tohoku University, Equipment-Institute for tuberculosis & Leporosy, 1959-1960 (Box 65, Folder 1006)
  - 60-552, Tohoku University, Books-Equipment-Library, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 1007)
  - 61-608, Tohoku University, Journals, General Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 65, Folder 1008)
  - 62-655. Tohoku University, Teaching Equipment-Pharmacology, General Correspondence-Local Purchases, 1962-1963 (Box 65, Folder 1009)
  - 63-703, Tohoku University, Journals-Library Equipment, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1962-1965 (Box 65, Folder 1010)
  - 63-704, Tohoku University, Biochemistry Equipment-Student Laboratories, 1963-1964 (Box 65, Folder 1011)
  - 65-853, Tohoku University, Library Support-Journals & Equipment, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1964-1967 (Box 65, Folder 1012)
  - 65-834-30, Tohoku University, Fellow, Arakawa, Tsuneo, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 1013)
  - CM 279-20, Tohoku University, Fellow, Ebina, Toshiaki, 1954-1955 (Box 65, Folder 1014)
  - 58-429-28, Tohoku University, Fellow, Kurokawa, Toshio, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 1015)
  - CM 241-15, Tohoku University, Fellow, Matsuda, Kojiro, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 1016)
  - CM 259-4, Tohoku University, Fellow, Motokawa, Kioti, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 1017)
  - 61-691-10, Tohoku University, Fellow, Murakami, Tsugio, 1961-1962 (Box 66, Folder 1018)
  - 67-938-37, Tohoku University, Fellow, Nagao, Koji, 1967-1968 (Box 66, Folder 1019)
  - 65-868-17, Tohoku University, Fellow, Nakao, Taisuke, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 1020)
  - CM 327-15, Tohoku University, Fellow, Sano, Tamotsu, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 1021)
  - 69-086-44, Tohoku University, Fellow, Suzuki, Hiroshi, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 1022)
  - 63-694-56, Tohoku University, Fellow, Suzuki, Taizo, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1023)
  - 63-694-37, Tohoku University, Fellow, Taira, Norio, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1024)
  - 60-541-20, Tohoku University, Fellow, Torikai, Tatsuo, 1956, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 1025)
  - 59-474-18, Tohoku University, Fellow, Yamagata, Shoichi, 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1026)
  - CM 259-8, Tohoku University, Fellow, Yoshioka, Kijiro, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 1027)
  - Cm 241-6, Tokyo Jikeikai School of Medicine, Fellow, Takaki, Fumikazu, 1951-1953 (Box 66, Folder 1028)
  - 57-425, Tokyo University, Library Construction, 1957-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1029)
  - 58-443, Tokyo University, Equipment-Physiology, 1958-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1030)
  - 62-663, Tokyo University, Library Support, General Correspondence & Original Orders, Local Purchases, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 1031)
  - 64-743, Tokyo University, Library Support-Books & Journals, 1963-1967 (Box 66, Folder 1032)
  - 64-744, Tokyo University, Equipment-Otolaryngology, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1033)
  - 67-946, Tokyo University, Equipment-Geriatrics & Microbiology, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1967, 1969-1970 (Box 66, Folder 1034)
  - CM 311-7, Tokyo University, Fellow, Doi, L. Takeo, 1955, 1958, 1962, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 1035)
  - CM 279-15, Tokyo University, Fellow, Hashimoto, Koroku, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 1036)
  - 67-938-43, Tokyo University, Fellow, Imamura, Keinosuke, 1967-1969, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 1037)
  - 64-762-9, Tokyo University, Fellow, Iwata, Kazuo, 1956, 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 1038)